

Contacts

Phone: +48 531 310 527 E-mail: witold.g83@gmail.com

Technical Skills

- HTMI
- CSS
- SOL
- C++
- InTouch
- Linux
- Python

Soft Skills

- Responsibility
- Easy contact with people
- Quick learning ability
- Teamwork

DOWNLOAD CV





Witold Grzesiak

Engineer

I am a graduate of the University of Zielona Góra, specializing in Industrial Automation. I am also a master's student in Computer Science at the same university. I'm passionate about new technologies and the use of AI in medicine.

Achievements

- 1. Social assistant to MP Anita Kucharska-Dziedzic
- 2. Canva Course Online graphics from scratch
- 3. <u>Linux Course for beginners</u>

Employment History

Junior Remote Service Support Specialist at Ekoenergetyka - Service

August 2023 – December 2024

- Remote diagnosis of charging stations
- Remote repair of electric chargers
- Support for service partners, customers, and technicians
- Remote software updates

Junior Specialist in Emergency Service

February 2023 – August 2023

- Repairing electric chargers
- Installing chargers
- Performing periodic inspections
- Diagnosing chargers

Service Assistant

July 2022 – February 2023

- Repairing electric chargers
- Installing chargers
- Performing periodic inspections

Hospitality Leader at FMD Jadwiga Wieczorek – McDonald's

June 2019 - May 2020

- Providing guests with information about the restaurant's current offers
- Maintaining cleanliness in the lobby
- Managing the cleaning team

Education

Computer Science, University of Zielona Góra

February 2023 – Present

Automation and Robotics, University of Zielona Góra

October 2019 – February 2023